Boateng Agyemang Patrick

+(233) 024-551-3607 +(233) 026-081-2576 kofiktechgh@gmail.com

Mobile and Web Applications Developer equipped with experience in cross-platform mobile applications and web development. Employs excellent leadership skills and multi-tasking strengths. Demonstrated ability to improve develop mobile applications with Flutter. Supportive and enthusiastic team player dedicated to streamlining processes and efficiently resolving project issues.

Experience

09/2022 to 07/2023

Mobile Applications Developer (Flutter)

Bestwin foods, Kumasi (Remote)

- Mobile app design and development while remaining concentrate on client needs.
- Cooperate diligently with other IT team members to plan, design, and develop smart solutions.
- Estimate user interface between hardware and software
- Answered customer questions and resolved service issues in a timely manner.
- Interacts with business analysts, developers, and technical support to determine optimal specifications.

09/2023 to 02/2024

Mobile Applications Developer (Flutter)

404 Solutions , Achimota-Accra

- Evaluated applications for efficiency gains and identified areas, boosting department workflow monthly.
- Enhanced bug detection rate by 93%.

02/2022 to 03/2023

Web Developer

Oka creations, Accra-Sakaman

- Create and modify mobile applications with service levels in mind.
- Discovered usability problems via 13 focus group meetings, 32 test cases analysis, and design, including 210 implementation reviews. Help out in production and deployment areas as needed and maintain comprehensive current knowledge of operations.

Highlights

- Results-oriented
- Operability and commitment
- Ability to motivate other team members and maintain good relations
- Resistance to stress
- Good manners

Education

Bachelor of Science: Information Technology - 2020 - 2024

University of Education Winneba Kumasi Campus (Now AAMUSTED-Kumasi), Ghana

Technologies

- Flutter & Dart
- Firebase
- NodeJs
- MongoDB